威尔 · 森坦斯: 请讲，马克。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Go ahead Mark.
Mark: 所以，就 JavaScript 而言，函数已经完成了。
&gt;&gt; Mark: So, as far as JavaScript
is concerned, the function is done.
所以，它朝着什么方向
So, that it's headed off for what
我们说的是-威尔 · 森坦斯: 哪个函数？
we're talking about-
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Which function?
马克: 打印，对不起，设定时间。
&gt;&gt; Mark: Print, I'm sorry, set time out.
威尔 · 森特斯: 设定时间，是的。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Set time out, yes.
或者在我们的外观之后，我们的功能触发网页浏览器的东西,
Or after our facade, our function that
triggers stuff in the web browser,
是的，是的。
yeah, yeah.
网页浏览器会直接影响堆栈
&gt;&gt; Mark: The web browser then is
directly affecting the stack at
一个晚些的日期-[声音]在一些-威尔森塔斯: 那似乎
a later date- [SOUND] In some-
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: That seems
很疯狂，对吧？
insane, right?
马克: 是的，这看起来很奇怪，如果堆栈里有东西怎么办？
&gt;&gt; Mark: Yeah, that seems strange and
what if the stack has got stuff in it?
威尔 · 森特斯: 马蒂说所有的调用堆栈,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: And so
Marty is saying all of the call stack,
如果我们运行一个函数,
what if we're running a function,
这个函数是不是只是在 JavaScript 中重新运行了一下？
does this- This function is only
just rock up back in JavaScript?
这不可能。
That can't be right.
是的，布莱登。
Yeah, Braden.
布雷顿: 那么零毫秒的例子呢？
&gt;&gt; Braydon: What about
the zero millisecond example?
布雷登: 那个人在哪里? 威尔 · 森坦斯: 是的，等一下。
&gt;&gt; Braydon: Where did that one-
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, hold on.
零毫秒怎么样？
What about zero milliseconds?
为什么函数不直接到这里
Why did the function not
just come out into here and
然后直接回家跑掉？
then come straight back home and run?
问得好，布莱登，杰森？
Great question Braden, Jason?
布雷顿: 对不起。
&gt;&gt; Braydon: Excuse me.
当我们转移它时，printHello 函数是设置时间和
The printHello function,
when we transfer it, is the set time and
我不记得实现的方法了，是设置超时记得这样的位
I don't remember the implementation,
is set timeout memorized so the bits that
编写 printHello，它们存储在我们会说这是 V8执行上下文吗？
make up printHello, are they stored in
we'll say it's the V8 execution context?
威尔 · 森特斯: 所以我们在这里暗示一些事情。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: So
here we're hinting at something around.
等等，这个 printHello 函数能够保持它周围的任何状态吗？
Hold on, does that printHello function
get to hold onto any state around it?
假设它需要使用周围的其他数据，那么这些数据会被保存吗？
Suppose it needs to use some other data
around it, does that data get held onto?
那么，你认为这些数据是从哪里来的呢？
Well, where do you think that
data gets held onto, people?
在哪里？
In the?
布雷顿: 背包 威尔 · 森特斯: 在背包里,
&gt;&gt; Braydon: Backpack.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: In the backpack,
没错。
exactly.
传播，传播。
Spreading, spreading.
布雷登: 便条还是威尔 · 森特斯: 那东西留在里面
&gt;&gt; Braydon: The note or-
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: That thing stays in
这是一个关于它存储在 JavaScript 中的地方的引用。
JavaScript, this is a reference back
to where it's stored in JavaScript.
是的，当然。
Yeah, absolutely.
是的，是的，printHello 函数并没有被复制到网页浏览器中。
Yeah, yeah, the printHello function is
not sort of copied into the web browser.
这是一个链接到它最初保存的地方,
It's a link back to where
it's originally saved,
也许包括所有周围的数据。
including maybe all
surrounding data as well.
好了，各位。
All right people.
所以，很明显，我们这里有一个问题，我们需要
So, clearly, we have a problem
here where we need to have
某种规则，当这个非凡的另一个
some sort of rules for
when this extraordinary other
在 JavaScript 中使用这个函数。
world is allowing this
function back into JavaScript.
布拉登暗示了这一点，马克暗示了这一点。
Braden hinted at this,
Mark hinted at this.
如果堆栈上还有其他代码怎么办？
What if I've got other
code on the stack here?
顺便说一下，如果我有一百万个控制台日志怎么办？
By the way, what if I've got
maybe a million console logs?
这个函数什么时候被允许返回？
When is this function allowed back in?
谈论不可预知的语言，任何时候都可能？
Talk about unpredictable language,
any time maybe?
如果我们现在与 JavaScript 之外的世界进行交互,
It turns out given we're interacting
with a world outside of JavaScript now,
我们需要一些非常非常严格的规定。
we're gonna need some really,
really strict rules.
他们真的很严格。
And they are really strict.
但是它让我们的代码变得超级可预测。
But it makes our code super predictable.
如果我们知道这些核心规则，我们就能从根本上知道它的行为。
We fundamentally know how it's gonna
behave if we know these core rules.
我们会看到这个代码。
So we're gonna see this code here.
我们有一个函数 printHello，一个函数 blockFor1Sec。
We've got a function printHello,
a function blockFor1Sec.
一秒钟的阻塞线程。
A block thread for one second.
它是怎么做到的呢，因为任何 JavaScript 中的缓慢任务,
How's it gonna do that because
any slow task in JavaScript,
它总是把它扔到网页浏览器的功能里。
it'll always throw it out
to the web browser feature.
如果我们想和互联网对话,
If we want to speak to the Internet,
我们要在网页浏览器的后台进行。
we're gonna do it in
the background of the web browser.
如果我们要做一个计时器，我们要在后台的网页浏览器，所以
If we wanna do a timer, we're gonna do it
in the background of the web browser so
我们不会阻止任何单线程语言的代码运行。
we don't block any further code in our
single threaded language from running.
那么我们怎样才能真正阻止 JavaScript 运行
So how could we actually block
JavaScript from running code for
比如，有没有人执行一个任务，结果阻止了代码的运行？
like a- have anyone does a task that
it ends up blocking code from running?
是的，彼得，说吧。
Yeah, Peter, go ahead.
彼得: 只要运行 for 循环。
&gt;&gt; Peter: Just run a for loop.
威尔 · 森特斯: 对于循环，杰森，你也要说同样的话吗？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: For loop, Jason,
you're gonna say the same thing?
彼得: 是的，对于循环，计时器，有事情要做。
&gt;&gt; Peter: Yeah, for loop,
timer, something to occupy.
威尔: 嗯，不是计时器，因为计时器会在这里发生。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Well, not a timer,
cuz a timer's gonna happen down here.
所以，一个 for 循环正如你所说的那样，Jason。
So, a for loop is exactly right
as you say as well, Jason.
它会阻塞线程一秒钟，所以可能是一个 for
It's gonna block the thread for
one second, so maybe like a for
循环添加我不知道，我需要找出这个。
loop adding I don't know,
I need to find this out.
也许在一个数组中加入三百万个元素,
Maybe adding like three
million elements to an array,
大概需要一秒钟。
that's gonna take maybe about a second.
我不会在这里写代码，但是
I'm not gonna write the code out here but
只要知道这就是那种黑盒子的功能。
just know that that's in that
kind of black box function there.
如果我们要运行它，它会坐在调用堆栈上做——因为你不能这样做
If we were to run it, it's gonna sit on
the call stack doing- because you can't do
一个长任务，但你可以做许多小的短任务。
one long task in JavaScript, but
you can do many tiny short tasks.
这就是我们如何阻止它的方法。
And that's how we can block it.
然后我们可以设定暂停顺便说一句,
Then we're gonna be able to set timeout,
we're already by the way,
对于 Braden 0毫秒等待并不陌生。
not unfamiliar with that with
Braden zero millisecond wait.
然后我们给我们的街区打个电话。
Then we're gonna call our block for
one second.
然后我们会先打电话。
And then we're gonna call first.
现在我当然假设,
Now I assume, of course,
printhello 会在0毫秒时运行。
the printHello is gonna run
immediately at zero milliseconds.
我们需要一些基本的规则
Mm-hm, we're gonna need to have
some pretty fundamental rules
我们的代码将如何运行
about how our code is going to run